Guide to the Roger Yockey Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Roger Yockey papers
1989-2011
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5825
5825-001
Yockey, Roger
.48 cubic feet
Research materials compiled by Yockey during the writing of his book, "People Are #1," on the Puget Sound Grocery Strike of 1989
Roger Yockey is a journalist and a retired union representative and community oganizer. Yockey was a communications officer for United Food and Commerical Workers Local during the 1989 strike. Author of: "The right of privacy and the right to report the news, 1965; "I never stopped believing", c2007. "People are # 1" c2010.
Research materials compiled by Yockey during the writing of his book, "People Are #1," on the Puget Sound Grocery Strike of 1989.
Open to all users.
Roger Yockey, 10/18/2013.
Yockey, Roger$vArchives; United Food and Commercial Workers International Union; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Strikes and lockouts$zWashington (State)$zPuget Sound; Strikes and lockouts$zWashington (State)$zPuget Sound; Grocery trade$xLabor unions$zWashington (State)$zPuget Sound; Meat industry and trade$xLabor unions$zWashington (State)$zPuget Sound; Strikes and lockouts$xGrocery trade; Strikes and lockouts$xMeat industry and trade; People are # 1; Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor Unions; Labor History; Washington (State); Journalism
- Series I: Photographs, May 1989-July 1989 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Photographs of 1989 Grocery Strike, May 1989-July 1989 (Box-folder 1/1)
- Series II: Sources and Publishers' Material for People Are #1, 1986-2011 (Box-folder 1/2-1/6, Oversized Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Press Clippings, Correspondence & Notes, 1986-2011 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Interviews, Notes & Drafts, 1986-2010 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Notes, Drafts & Sources, 1989-2010 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Sources & Drafts, 1989-2010 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - The Picket Liner & Newspapers, 1989-2009 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Articles on 1989 Puget Sound Strike, Issues of The Unifier, publication of The National Rank-and-File Against Concessions. Critical of the UFCW's cooperation with Hormel and its takeover of Local P-9 in Austin, Minnesota., 1986 (Box-folder Misc. oversized box 4, folder 2)
- Series III: 1995 Senior Thesis on 1989 Strike (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Crain, Tom "The UFCW and the Strike of '89", 1995 (Box-folder 1/7)
- Series IV: Newspaper Articles by Roger Yockey, 1969 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Tyree Scott & Central Contractors Association, 1969 (Box-folder 1/8)